Aishna Kumar

Quality Auditor

I am a professional with 6 years of experience in various domains like Sales, Customer Service, Collections and Auditing, working for Global Organization. Having excellent command on verbal and written communication with strong interpersonal and presentation skills and open to work in a changing environment.

Work History

2022-06 -Current

Technical Quality Consultant

MattsenKumar LLC, Gurugram

- Audit calls for the agents who are working for HP customer service in USA and Canada.
- Auditing Calls based on various attributes which includescritical areas like Professionalism, PII verification, etc., Attitude, Communication and many more.
- Calls are audited by the Speech Miner tool and the evaluationis done in the NEQQO tool and the data is verified using different tools which are supported by HP i.e., CDAX, AST (Agent Support Tool) which is used to check the data for a special project for which HP works i.e., INSTANT INK.
- The calls which are audited comes from the USA and Canadafor HP printers, HP computers, HP laptop.
- The audited reports are submitted to the managers which arelater sent to the Client (HP).

2021-06 -2022-06

Senior Technical Support

GNS GLOBAL PVT. LTD., Gurugram

- Maintained excellent customer satisfaction by delivering highqualitycustomer service and dealing with all matters appropriately.
- Responded to customer emails, calls and live chat regarding technicalmalfunctions and issues to fix remotely.
- Installed and set up applications for clients, including antivirussoftware and Microsoft Office.
- Helped customers set up new systems, computers, applications, andsoftware.
- Provided clear and concise step-by-step technical support.

Contact

Address

Flat No. 4104/4105 Vardhman Tower 1, Jurs Country Jwalapur, Haridwar, 249407

Phone

+91-9760251420

E-mail

kumaraishna225@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/aishna-kumar-538118267

Skills

- Microsoft Office Suite
- Quick Learner
- Technical Writing
- Excellent Oral and Verbal Communication
- Business requirements understanding
- Possess the ability to adapt to changes.

Languages

- English
- Hindi

2019-06 -2021-05

Sales and Marketing Co-ordinator

Gulshan LameePack Pvt. Ltd., Haridwar

- Setting up meetings with potential clients and responding to their queriesand concerns and finding new clients through various contacts and meeting them to explain about the quality of the product (corrugated boxes) to the clients like Automat Irrigation, Creative, TCPL, etc.
- Preparing and delivering appropriate presentations on product details and services and updating the existing clients about the updates about the product and for new business development, presenting theused product and the technology.
- Creating frequent reviews and sales and gross profit reports on daily basisto see if the daily target has been achieved or not.
- Ensuring the availability of stock for sales and demonstrations and maintaining the stock using TALLY ERP-9
- Working towards achieving monthly or annual targets. Reached 92% monthly target and also received the best salesperson in the month of January-February 2021

2017-08 -2018-11

Sales Executive

Tech Matrix software Solutions Pvt. Ltd., Gurugram

- Reviewing sales performance and analyzing if the team has reached thetargeted value or not.
- Working towards achieving monthly or annual targets
- Reached 80% of the targeted weekly sales and distributed incentives accordingly.
- Negotiating and closing deals and handling complaints or objections
- Problem solving percentage varied between 70%-75%.

2017-01-2017-08

Sales Executive

Saburi TLC, Gurugram

- Actively seek out new sales opportunities through cold calling and networking with new clients for achieving new business deals.
- Handling client meetings with the linked clients and the new clients for the new business.
- Demonstrating and presenting products by explaining about the softwarelike Mac cleaner, Anti-virus etc.

Education

2012-07 -2016-06 Bachelor of Technology: Electronics and Communication Engineering

Lovely Professional University- Jalandhar, India

Accomplishments

- Participated in the 'Cultural Evening Fest', Delhi Public School
- 2011 Vice House Captain, Delhi Public School, 2011-2012
- Participated in the inter-state dance competition, Lovely Professional University
- 2013Represented Girls Hostel in the event 'Incredible-8, Lovely Professional University
- 2015 Received the bronze medal CGPA above 8, Delhi Public School, 2010
- Event Manager for the event 'Incredible-8', Lovely Professional University, 2015

Certifications

Certificate in Digital Marketing from UpGrad